{
   "name":"quiz4",
   "que0":[
      {
         "question":"Are you ready to enter the Gateway To A New World?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Yes",
            "b":"No"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      }
   ],
   "que1":[
      {
         "question":"Does crypto generate you an income? Does crypto replace your job?",
         "options":{
            "a":"No",
            "b":"Yes"
         },
         "answer":"b"
      }
   ],
   "que2":[
      {
         "question":"You can succeed at anything if you:",
         "options":{
            "a":"Never quit and become super skilled at what we know works",
            "b":"Jump from thing to thing because you're easily distracted",
            "c":"Follow what's currently popular, just like everyone else",
            "d":"Become emotional and impatient that you didn't make $100k in 3.5 weeks"
         },
         "answer":"a"
      }
   ],
   "que3":[
      {
         "question":"If you want to learn what actually makes you money you must:",
         "options":{
            "a":"Cry",
            "b":"Learn what everyone else already knows",
            "c":"Complain",
            "d":"Progress to the more advanced lessons"
         },
         "answer":"d"
      }
   ],
   "que4":[
      {
         "question":"How do you become a professional and avoid gambling like a degenerate?",
         "options":{
            "a":"The spirits of the universe will guide me",
            "b":"By guessing, because using your brain is hard",
            "c":"By buying NFT's",
            "d":"By studying the lessons every day"
         },
         "answer":"d"
      }
   ],
   "que5":[
      {
         "question":"To invest in crypto under 18 you must use:",
         "options":{
            "a":"Fraud to open an account",
            "b":"Excuses to avoid making an account",
            "c":"A custodial app, or your parents account"
         },
         "answer":"c"
      }
   ],
   "que6":[
      {
         "question":"The effort you put into your questions is:",
         "options":{
            "a":"Not important",
            "b":"Something which can be winged",
            "c":"Super important",
            "d":"Meh"
         },
         "answer":"c"
      }
   ],
   "que7":[
      {
         "question":"By doing lessons and unlocking more advanced chats, you:",
         "options":{
            "a":"Jump from thing to thing because you're easily distracted",
            "b":"Gain the knowledge and motivation of more advanced students in the community",
            "c":"Become emotional and impatient that you didn't make $100k in 3.5 weeks",
            "d":"Follow what's currently popular on TikTok, just like everyone else"
         },
         "answer":"b"
      }
   ],
   "que8":[
      {
         "question":"How do you gain access to more signals?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Give a good signal in the chats to students",
            "b":"SComplete the Fundamental Lessons",
            "c":"Message the Professors",
            "d":"Showing us your Crypto portfolio balance"
         },
         "answer":"b"
      },
      {
         "question":"What do you do if you get lost?",
         "options":{
            "a":"Panic",
            "b":"Show everyone your favorite crypto coin",
            "c":"Spam all the chats",
            "d":"Check the campus map or ask for help in the #network channel"
         },
         "answer":"d"
      },
      {
         "question":"Now that you've finished the tutorials, where do you go to find the important Fundamental Lessons?",
         "options":{
            "a":"At the bottom of a pint of beer",
            "b":"In your pocket",
            "c":"In the \"Crypto Campus\" inside the #fundamentals channel"
         },
         "answer":"c"
      }
   ]
}